>> Brian Holt: 恭喜。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Congratulations.
你学会了 React
You have learned React.
我说我教了你 95 % 的
I would say I taught you
probably 95% of what's
React 的有用信息，可能是所有 React的 80% 。
useful about React and
probably 80% of all of React.
这其实是我喜欢的事情之一
And this is actually one of
the things that I like about it is
你可以把所有 React 都保留在你的头上对吧
that you can keep all of
React in your head, right?
它是一个相当小的图书馆，仅仅是原始的学习概念。
It's a fairly small library,
in terms of just raw concepts to learn.
而这就是我和 Angular 合作的时候的批评
Whereas this was my criticism with
Angular when I was working with it,
你不可能知道所有角
you can't know all of Angular.
这太重要了
It's just too big.
有太多的问题你不能一直保持在你的脑子里
There's just too much that it does and
you can't keep that all in your head.
那就好，有很多很酷的东西，和安珀一样，对吧 ?
That's fine, it does a lot of really
cool stuff, and same with Ember, right?
知道如何写 " 安珀 " 的人能够非常地相信
People that know how to write Ember
are able to scath out really incredible
项目。
projects.
我很欣赏他们的生产力
I admire them for
how productive they can be.
但我不太仔细地看 " React " ，因为它是
But I don't really look at the React aux
very much because it's something that if
你做得够多了就像坐在你脑袋里一样
you do enough,
it just kinda all sits in your head.
所以我写了一段很长时间的 React 。
So I've written React for a long time.
我是个大粉丝
I'm a big fan.
即使我不是在写作，我通常是在写  。
Even when I'm not writing React,
I'm usually writing Preact.
所以，之前的课程版本，我教了什么 Preact ， js 是什么。
[LAUGH] So, previous versions of this
course, I taught what Preact,js is.
这很可能值得我们去看看
It's something probably
worth checking out.
我今天不教它因为 Preact 总是落后于人
I'm not gonna teach it today because
Preact always lags behind React a little
，所以他们还没有准备好挂钩，上次我看的时候。
bit, and so they're still not ready
with hooks, last time I checked.
他们现在可能是但
They might be now, but.
如果你想写雷法
If you wanna write React but
如果只使用 3 千字节 ( 而不是 35 千字节 ) ，那么 Preact 将执行此操作。
have it only use 3 kilobytes instead
of 35 kilobytes, Preact will do that.
所以它是一个较小的，通常较慢的库，
So it's a smaller,
typically slower library,
一旦它执行，下载速度也会更快。
once it's executing, but
it's also faster to download.
因此，如果您尝试将 2G 网络和之类的内容作为目标，那么这一点非常有用。
So this is really useful if you're trying
to target 2G networks and stuff like that.
好消息是它的运作方式几乎完全一样。
And the good news is it works
almost exactly the same way.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 其实是到时时之间，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's actually
to the point where oftentimes,
你可以直接掉在 Preact ，这很酷，就可以了。
you can actually just drop in Preact,
which is pretty cool, and it'll just work.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 太棒了，那就是 " 复行 " 的结尾。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah great, so
that is the end of the intro to React.
再教这个太有趣了
This was so fun to teach this again.
这是我最喜欢的教学工作坊之一所以我做了这五个
It's one of my favorite workshop to teach,
hence, why I've done this five and
半天， [ LAUGH]。
a half times, [LAUGH].
如果他们不把我扔出去我估计也会再回来的
And I probably will be back again,
if they don't throw me out.
也很缓慢的更新。
It's also pretty slow to update as well.
在这种感觉中
In the sense of like,
五年前的反应还是和我们今天写的差不多。
the React of five years ago is still
pretty similar to what we write today.
我觉得写一个项目是个很好的方法
And yeah, I think it's a good
way to write a project.
所以这里有很多美好的地方。
So there's a lot of good places
where you can go from here.
我们将在这个项目上建立中间的 " 反应 " 。
There's intermediate React, which we'll
be building on this same project.
但是我们要做一些随意的事情比如情绪
But we're gonna go ahead and introduce
kind of optional things like emotion,
或服务器端呈现，或 Redux，或类似的内容。
or server-side rendering, or
Redux, or things like that.
你可以去参加肯特的测试课程
You can go take Kent's testing course.
我在中间 React 中有一个测试模块但它是这么大的
So I have a testing module in
the intermediate React, but it's this big,
激烈的，肯特的课程很深入的测试。
intense, and
Kent's course is very in-depth on testing.
史蒂夫有先进的国家管理
There's advanced state
management with Steve.
而且他做的工作比雷迪克斯和莫巴克斯
And he does a great job of going
over things like Redux and MobX and
有些很重的国家集装箱
some of those other very
heavy state containers.
然后在 FrontendMasters上还有其他很酷的东西。
And then there's just a lot of other
really cool stuff on FrontendMasters.
好的谢谢你的收看
So, yeah, thanks for watching.
谢谢你和我一起
Thanks for sticking with me.
>> [APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; [APPLAUSE]